A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, English Mental Hygiene Program, SG 1, Series 16 FA288
Rockefeller Archive Center
Commonwealth Fund records, English Mental Hygiene Program, SG 1, Series 16
1927-1947
Rockefeller Archive Center
Commonwealth Fund
FA288
10 Cubic Feet 26 boxes
Conditions Governing Access note
Open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
Biographical/Historical note
The Commonwealth Fund was established in 1918 with an endowment of $10 million from Mrs. Stephen V. Harkness for "benevolent, religious, educational and like purposes." The early grants supported a variety of programs while generally promoting welfare, especially child welfare. Several grants were made in the field of medical research, but the Board of Directors decided in 1920 that this field was already sufficiently supported by other philanthropic organizations.
Despite this decision, by the mid-1920s the chief interest of the Fund had become public health, including mental hygiene, community health, rural hospitals, medical research, and medical education. Other grant areas included war relief, educational and legal research, child welfare, and international medical fellowships.
File Plan note
Former Classification: IX; IV 4B 4
Scope and Contents note
During a visit to the United States in 1925, Mrs. St. Loe Strachey observed the work of the Philadelphia Child Guidance Clinic, one of the CF's demonstration clinics. Impressed by the activities of the Clinic, Mrs. Strachey inquired whether the CF might undertake a similar program in England. After her return to England she interested a number of individuals in her proposal and chaired a committee designed to implement her ideas. At the invitation of this committee, Mildred C. Scoville visited England in June 1926. The Fund then invited twelve key individuals to observe American child guidance techniques, and later enabled five English social workers to come to New York for training in psychiatric social work at the Institute for Child Guidance and the New York School of Social Work.
The Child Guidance Council (CGC) was organized in 1927 in London and included representatives of various groups concerned with the mental and physical health of children. The Council assumed responsibility for a program which included the establishment of a child guidance clinic in London, the training of psychiatric social workers, and the carrying on of general educational work in the mental health field.
The London Child Guidance Clinic opened in 1929, its staff having been trained in the United States during 1928 and early 1929. Arrangements were made by the CGC for a training course for psychiatric social workers at the London School of Economics, with a number of scholarships being provided by the CF. The CGC also offered fellowships in psychiatry and psychology. In 1930 the London clinic became an independent body with its own administrative and medical board, and the CGC emphasized other educational work and assistance in the development of clinics throughout England and in the improvement of standards of service. The London School of Economics utilized the London clinic for much of its field training. The CF supplied the major financial support of the entire project until 1931-1932 and thereafter withdrew gradually.
World War II forced the closure of the London clinic in 1939 and the mental health program was disrupted throughout the war years. After the war, however, advances in child guidance work rapidly developed. The Child Guidance Council, the National Council for Mental Hygiene, the Central Association for Mental Welfare, and the Mental Health Emergency Committee merged into the National Association for Mental Health, an organization financed entirely from British sources. The London School of Economics underwrote the costs of the mental health training courses, and the clinic resumed operation with funds from various sources, including a grant from the British Ministry of Health.
Other Finding Aids
Other available finding aids describing the Commonwealth Fund records include:
FA247 Commonwealth Fund Harkness House drawings
FA276 Commonwealth Fund records, Annual Reports, SG 1, Series 4
FA277 Commonwealth Fund records, Archives/Library, SG 1, Series 5
FA278 Commonwealth Fund records, Austrian Program, SG 1, Series 6
FA279 Commonwealth Fund records, Board of Directors, SG 1, Series 7
FA280 Commonwealth Fund records, Capital Grants, SG 1, Series 8
FA281 Commonwealth Fund records, Child Health Demonstrations, SG 1, Series 9
FA282 Commonwealth Fund records, Division of Community Clinics, SG 1, Series 10
FA283 Commonwealth Fund records, Division of Health Studies, SG 1, Series 11
FA284 Commonwealth Fund records, Division of Public Health, SG 1, Series 12
FA285 Commonwealth Fund records, Division of Publications, SG 1, Series 13
FA286 Commonwealth Fund records, Division of Rural Hospitals, SG 1, Series 14
FA287 Commonwealth Fund records, Educational Research, SG 1, Series 15
FA288 Commonwealth Fund records, English Mental Hygiene Program, SG 1, Series 16
FA289 Commonwealth Fund records, Finance Committee, SG 1, Series 17
FA290 Commonwealth Fund records, Grants, SG 1, Series 18
FA291 Commonwealth Fund records, Harkness Family, SG 1, Series 19
FA292 Commonwealth Fund records, Harkness Fellowships, SG 1, Series 20
FA428 Commonwealth Fund records, Harkness Fellowships, Fellows Reports, SG 1, Series 20A
FA293 Commonwealth Fund records, Institute for Child Guidance, SG 1, Series 21
FA294 Commonwealth Fund records, Interface Program, SG 1, Series 22
FA295 Commonwealth Fund records, Legal Research Program, SG 1, Series 23
FA296 Commonwealth Fund records, Living at Home Program, SG 1, Series 24
FA297 Commonwealth Fund records, Mental Hygiene Program, SG 1, Series 25
FA298 Commonwealth Fund records, Miscellaneous - unprocessed
FA299 Commonwealth Fund records, Personnel - unprocessed
FA300 Commonwealth Fund records, Pilgrim Trust, SG 1, Series 28
FA301 Commonwealth Fund records, Program for the Prevention of Delinquency, SG 1, Series 29
FA302 Commonwealth Fund records, Reference Files, SG 1, Series 30
FA303 Commonwealth Fund records, Reports of the General Director, SG 1, Series 31
FA304 Commonwealth Fund records, Treasurer, SG 1, Series 32
FA305 Commonwealth Fund records, Turndown Lists, SG 1, Series 33 - unprocessed
FA306 Commonwealth Fund records, Vertical File (R. Fitz), SG 1, Series 34 - unprocessed
FA307 Commonwealth Fund records, Visual Materials, SG 1, Series 35
FA389 Commonwealth Fund records, Administration - Historical Files, SG 1, Series 1
FA390 Commonwealth Fund records, Administration - Officers Files, SG 1, Series 2
FA429 Commonwealth Fund records, President, Margaret E. Mahoney, SG 2, Series 1
FA430 Commonwealth Fund records, Book Program, SG 2, Series 2
Child psychology; Child welfare; New York (N.Y.); Child mental health; Public health; New York (State); United States; Public welfare; Medical research; Medicine, Rural; Medicine -- Scholarships, fellowships, etc.; Legal research; Mental health; Medical education; Law; Legal issues; Education, Rural; Hygiene; War relief
- Child Guidance Council (CGC) - American Personnel in England - Correspondence, 1941-1942 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Child Guidance Council (CGC) - Annual Reports, 1927-1943 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Child Guidance Council (CGC) - Annual Reports, 1927-1943 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Child Guidance Council (CGC) - Annual Reports (Correspondence), 1933-1938 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Child Guidance Council (CGC) - Budget Correspondence, 1927-1941 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Child Guidance Council (CGC) - Budget Correspondence, 1927-1941 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Child Guidance Council (CGC) - Budget Correspondence, 1927-1941 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Child Guidance Council (CGC) - Correspondence - Individual (B-L), 1928-1935 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Child Guidance Council (CGC) - Correspondence - Individual (M-R), 1928-1935 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Child Guidance Council (CGC) - Correspondence - Individual (S-W), 1928-1935 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Child Guidance Council (CGC) - Correspondence - Secretary/CGC, 1927-1928 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Child Guidance Council (CGC) - Correspondence - Secretary/CGC, 1927-1928 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Child Guidance Council (CGC) - Correspondence - Secretary/CGC, 1928-1932 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Child Guidance Council (CGC) - Correspondence - Secretary/CGC, 1928-1932 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Child Guidance Council (CGC) - Correspondence - Secretary/CGC, 1928-1932 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Child Guidance Council (CGC) - Correspondence - Secretary/CGC, 1928-1932 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Child Guidance Council (CGC) - Correspondence - Secretary/CGC, 1928-1932 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Child Guidance Council (CGC) - Correspondence - Secretary/CGC, 1928-1932 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Child Guidance Council (CGC) - Correspondence - Secretary/CGC, 1928-1932 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Child Guidance Council (CGC) - Correspondence - Secretary/CGC, 1928-1932 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Child Guidance Council (CGC) - Correspondence - Secretary/CGC, 1928-1932 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Child Guidance Council (CGC) - Correspondence - Secretary/CGC, 1928-1932 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Child Guidance Council (CGC) - Correspondence - Secretary/CGC, 1928-1932 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Child Guidance Council (CGC) - Correspondence - Secretary/CGC, 1928-1932 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Child Guidance Council (CGC) - Correspondence - Secretary/CGC, 1933-1939 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Child Guidance Council (CGC) - Correspondence - Secretary/CGC, 1933-1939 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Child Guidance Council (CGC) - Correspondence - Secretary/CGC, 1933-1939 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Child Guidance Council (CGC) - Correspondence - Secretary/CGC, 1933-1939 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Child Guidance Council (CGC) - Correspondence - Secretary/CGC, 1933-1939 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Child Guidance Council (CGC) - Correspondence - Secretary/CGC, 1933-1939 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Child Guidance Council (CGC) - Correspondence - Secretary/CGC, 1933-1939 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Child Guidance Council (CGC) - Correspondence - Secretary/CGC, 1933-1939 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Child Guidance Council (CGC) - Correspondence - Secretary/CGC, 1933-1939 (Box 3, Folder 33)
- Child Guidance Council (CGC) - Courses for Medical Officers, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 34)
  Scope and Contents note
  Correspondence - March 30, 1933-February 27, 1934 Reports - February 1934 and July 1936
- Child Guidance Council (CGC) - Fellowships in Psychiatry and Psychology - Correspondence, 1930-1936; June 16-27, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 35)
- Child Guidance Council (CGC) - Financial Correspondence and Data, 1927-1945 (Box 4, Folder 36)
- Child Guidance Council (CGC) - Financial Correspondence and Data, 1927-1945 (Box 4, Folder 37)
- Child Guidance Council (CGC) - Financial Correspondence and Data, 1927-1945 (Box 4, Folder 38)
- Child Guidance Council (CGC) - Financial Correspondence and Data, 1927-1945 (Box 4, Folder 39)
- Child Guidance Council (CGC) - Financial Correspondence and Data, 1927-1945 (Box 4, Folder 40)
- Child Guidance Council (CGC) - Financial Correspondence and Data, 1927-1945 (Box 4, Folder 41)
- Child Guidance Council (CGC) - Financial Correspondence and Data, 1927-1945 (Box 4, Folder 42)
- Child Guidance Council (CGC) - Financial Correspondence and Data, 1927-1945 (Box 4, Folder 43)
- Child Guidance Council (CGC) - Financial Correspondence and Data, 1927-1945 (Box 4, Folder 44)
- Child Guidance Council (CGC) - Financial Correspondence and Data, 1927-1945 (Box 4, Folder 45)
- Child Guidance Council (CGC) - General Secretary Survey Reports, 1931-1933 (Box 4, Folder 46)
- Child Guidance Council (CGC) - General Secretary Survey Reports, 1934-1939 (Box 5, Folder 47)
- Child Guidance Council (CGC) - Inter-clinic Meetings - Correspondence, Minutes and Reports, 1933-1939 (Box 5, Folder 48)
- Child Guidance Council (CGC) - Interoffice Memoranda, 1928-1938 (Box 5, Folder 49)
- Child Guidance Council (CGC) - Loan Service to Clinics - Birmingham (Correspondence and Memoranda), 1930-1933 (Box 5, Folder 50)
- Child Guidance Council (CGC) - Loan Service to Clinics - General Correspondence, 1929-1932 (Box 5, Folder 51)
- Child Guidance Council (CGC) - Loan Service to Clinics - General Correspondence, 1929-1932 (Box 5, Folder 52)
- Child Guidance Council (CGC) - Loan Service to Clinics - General Correspondence, 1929-1932 (Box 5, Folder 53)
- Child Guidance Council (CGC) - Loan Service to Clinics - General Correspondence, 1929-1932 (Box 5, Folder 54)
- Child Guidance Council (CGC) - Loan Service to Clinics - General Correspondence, 1929-1932 (Box 5, Folder 55)
- Child Guidance Council (CGC) - Loan Service to Clinics - General Correspondence, 1929-1932 (Box 5, Folder 56)
- Child Guidance Council (CGC) - Loan Service to Clinics - General Correspondence, 1929-1932 (Box 5, Folder 57)
- Child Guidance Council (CGC) - Loan Service to Clinics - General Correspondence, 1933-1939 (Box 6, Folder 58)
- Child Guidance Council (CGC) - Loan Service to Clinics - General Correspondence, 1933-1939 (Box 6, Folder 59)
- Child Guidance Council (CGC) - Loan Service to Clinics - General Correspondence, 1933-1939 (Box 6, Folder 60)
- Child Guidance Council (CGC) - Loan Service to Clinics - General Correspondence, 1933-1939 (Box 6, Folder 61)
- Child Guidance Council (CGC) - Loan Service to Clinics - Reports-Clinics, 1939-1942 (Box 6, Folder 62)
- Child Guidance Council (CGC) - Loan Service to Clinics - Reports-Loan Staff, 1927-1939 (Box 6, Folder 63)
- Child Guidance Council (CGC) - Loan Service to Clinics - Reports-Social Workers (B-H), 1931-1939 (Box 6, Folder 64)
- Child Guidance Council (CGC) - Loan Service to Clinics - Reports-Social Workers (K-U), 1931-1939 (Box 6, Folder 65)
- Child Guidance Council (CGC) - Mailing Lists and Form Letters, 1928-1937 (Box 6, Folder 66)
- Child Guidance Council (CGC) - Membership Lists, 1928-1939 (Box 6, Folder 67)
- Child Guidance Council (CGC) - Minutes - Ad Hoc Committee on the Future of Mental Health of Childhood, June-July, 1942 (Box 6, Folder 68)
- Child Guidance Council (CGC) - Minutes - Child Guidance Council, 1926-1933 (Box 7, Folder 69)
- Child Guidance Council (CGC) - Minutes - Child Guidance Council, 1926-1933 (Box 7, Folder 70)
- Child Guidance Council (CGC) - Minutes - Child Guidance Council, 1926-1933 (Box 7, Folder 71)
- Child Guidance Council (CGC) - Minutes - Executive Committee, 1933-1938 (Box 7, Folder 72)
- Child Guidance Council (CGC) - Minutes - Executive Committee, 1933-1938 (Box 7, Folder 73)
- Child Guidance Council (CGC) - Minutes - Executive Committee, 1933-1938 (Box 7, Folder 74)
- Child Guidance Council (CGC) - Minutes - Executive Committee, 1933-1938 (Box 7, Folder 75)
- Child Guidance Council (CGC) - Minutes - Executive Committee, 1933-1938 (Box 7, Folder 76)
- Child Guidance Council (CGC) - Minutes - Executive Committee, 1933-1938 (Box 7, Folder 77)
- Child Guidance Council (CGC) - Minutes - Executive Committee, 1939-1944 (Box 8, Folder 78)
- Child Guidance Council (CGC) - Minutes - Executive Committee, 1939-1944 (Box 8, Folder 79)
- Child Guidance Council (CGC) - Minutes - Executive Committee, 1939-1944 (Box 8, Folder 80)
- Child Guidance Council (CGC) - Minutes - Finance and General Purposes Committee, 1929-1932; June 7, 1939 (Box 8, Folder 81)
- Child Guidance Council (CGC) - Minutes - Finance and General Purposes Committee, 1929-1932; June 7, 1939 (Box 8, Folder 82)
- Child Guidance Council (CGC) - Minutes - Finance and General Purposes Committee, 1929-1932; June 7, 1939 (Box 8, Folder 83)
- Child Guidance Council (CGC) - Minutes - Miscellaneous Committees, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 84)
  Ad Hoc Committee on the Training of Play Therapists - January 1, 1939-May 17, 1939 Administrative Committee (Inter-Clinic) - June 15, 1939 Inter-Clinic Committee - June 7, 1939 Propaganda Sub-Committee - May 17, 1939
- Child Guidance Council (CGC) - Minutes - Subcommittees, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 85)
  Advisory Committee on Child Guidance Social Work - January 8, 1930-February 19, 1930 Clinic Committee - June 26, 1929-July 7, 1930 Committee for Co-Operation with Independent Clinics - January 7, 1930 Hospitals and Clinics Committee - November 10, 1930-December 16, 1930
- Child Guidance Council (CGC) - Minutes - Subcommittees, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 86)
  Medical Committee - December 16, 1930-May 31, 1944
- Child Guidance Council (CGC) - Minutes - Subcommittees, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 87)
  Psychological and Educational Committee - November 11, 1930-June 14, 1939 Training Committee - May 22, 1929-January 8, 1930
- Child Guidance Council (CGC) - Miscellaneous Reports, 1928-1938 (Box 9, Folder 88)
- Child Guidance Council (CGC) - Miscellaneous Reports, 1928-1938 (Box 9, Folder 89)
- Child Guidance Council (CGC) - Statistical Data on Psychiatric Social Workers, 1932-1934 (Box 9, Folder 90)
- Child Guidance Council (CGC) - War Emergency Plans - Correspondence, 1938-1947 (Box 9, Folder 91)
- Child Guidance Council (CGC) - War Emergency Plans - Correspondence, 1938-1947 (Box 9, Folder 92)
- Child Guidance Council (CGC) - War Emergency Plans - Correspondence, 1938-1947 (Box 9, Folder 93)
- Child Guidance Council (CGC) - War Emergency Plans - Correspondence, 1938-1947 (Box 9, Folder 94)
- Child Guidance Council (CGC) - War Emergency Plans - Correspondence, 1938-1947 (Box 9, Folder 95)
- London Child Guidance Clinic and Training Center - Annual Reports and Correspondence, 1931-1938 (Box 9, Folder 96)
- London Child Guidance Clinic and Training Center - Audits and Correspondence, 1931-1942 (Box 9, Folder 97)
- London Child Guidance Clinic and Training Center - Budget Data and Correspondence, 1931-1940 (Box 9, Folder 98)
- London Child Guidance Clinic and Training Center - Feversham, Lord - Correspondence, 1936-1939 (Box 10, Folder 99)
- London Child Guidance Clinic and Training Center - Financial Correspondence and Statements, 1929-1939 (Box 10, Folder 100)
- London Child Guidance Clinic and Training Center - Financial Correspondence and Statements, 1929-1939 (Box 10, Folder 101)
- London Child Guidance Clinic and Training Center - Financial Correspondence and Statements, 1929-1939 (Box 10, Folder 102)
- London Child Guidance Clinic and Training Center - Financial Correspondence and Statements, 1929-1939 (Box 10, Folder 103)
- London Child Guidance Clinic and Training Center - Financial Correspondence and Statements, 1929-1939 (Box 10, Folder 104)
- London Child Guidance Clinic and Training Center - Financial Correspondence and Statements, 1929-1939 (Box 10, Folder 105)
- London Child Guidance Clinic and Training Center - Financial Correspondence and Statements, 1929-1939 (Box 10, Folder 106)
- London Child Guidance Clinic and Training Center - General Correspondence, 1925-1927 (Box 10, Folder 107)
- London Child Guidance Clinic and Training Center - General Correspondence, 1925-1927 (Box 10, Folder 108)
- London Child Guidance Clinic and Training Center - General Correspondence, 1925-1927 (Box 10, Folder 109)
- London Child Guidance Clinic and Training Center - General Correspondence, 1928-1941, 1956, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 110)
- London Child Guidance Clinic and Training Center - General Correspondence, 1928-1941, 1956, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 111)
- London Child Guidance Clinic and Training Center - General Correspondence, 1928-1941, 1956, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 112)
- London Child Guidance Clinic and Training Center - General Correspondence, 1928-1941, 1956, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 113)
- London Child Guidance Clinic and Training Center - General Correspondence, 1928-1941, 1956, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 114)
- London Child Guidance Clinic and Training Center - General Correspondence, 1928-1941, 1956, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 115)
- London Child Guidance Clinic and Training Center - General Correspondence, 1928-1941, 1956, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 116)
- London Child Guidance Clinic and Training Center - General Correspondence, 1928-1941, 1956, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 117)
- London Child Guidance Clinic and Training Center - General Correspondence, 1928-1941, 1956, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 118)
- London Child Guidance Clinic and Training Center - General Correspondence, 1928-1941, 1956, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 119)
- London Child Guidance Clinic and Training Center - General Correspondence, 1928-1941, 1956, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 120)
- London Child Guidance Clinic and Training Center - General Correspondence, 1928-1941, 1956, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 121)
- London Child Guidance Clinic and Training Center - Lawrence, Lady (Isabel) - Correspondence, 1928-1935 (Box 11, Folder 122)
- London Child Guidance Clinic and Training Center - Medical Director's Reports, 1930-1934 (Box 12, Folder 123)
- London Child Guidance Clinic and Training Center - Medical Director's Reports, 1930-1934 (Box 12, Folder 124)
- London Child Guidance Clinic and Training Center - Medical Director's Reports, 1930-1934 (Box 12, Folder 125)
- London Child Guidance Clinic and Training Center - Minutes - Administrative Committee/Board, 1930-1934; 1937-1938 (Box 12, Folder 126)
- London Child Guidance Clinic and Training Center - Minutes (Box 12, Folder 127)
  Board of Finance - March 28 and June 20, 1935 Board of Governors - January 21, 1937-October 20, 1938 Executive Board - May 16-July 18, 1935 and February 10, 1936
- London Child Guidance Clinic and Training Center - Minutes - Joint Board, 1932-1935 (Box 12, Folder 128)
- London Child Guidance Clinic and Training Center - Minutes - Joint Board, 1932-1935 (Box 12, Folder 129)
- London Child Guidance Clinic and Training Center - Minutes - Miscellaneous Committees (Box 12, Folder 130)
  Appointments Sub-committee - May 15, 1934 Cash Committee - February 26, 1936 Medical Committee - October 14, 1930-November 16, 1933
- London Child Guidance Clinic and Training Center - Miscellaneous Reports, 1930-1936; May 1965 (Box 12, Folder 131)
- London Child Guidance Clinic and Training Center - Moodie, William - Correspondence, 1929-1936 (Box 13, Folder 132)
- London Child Guidance Clinic and Training Center - Moodie, William - Correspondence, 1929-1936 (Box 13, Folder 133)
- London Child Guidance Clinic and Training Center - Moodie, William - Correspondence, 1929-1936 (Box 13, Folder 134)
- London Child Guidance Clinic and Training Center - Moodie, William - Correspondence, 1929-1936 (Box 13, Folder 135)
- London Child Guidance Clinic and Training Center - Moodie, William - Correspondence, 1929-1936 (Box 13, Folder 136)
- London Child Guidance Clinic and Training Center - Moodie, William - Correspondence, 1929-1936 (Box 13, Folder 137)
- London Child Guidance Clinic and Training Center - Moodie, William - Correspondence, 1929-1936 (Box 13, Folder 138)
- London Child Guidance Clinic and Training Center - Moodie, William - Correspondence, 1929-1936 (Box 13, Folder 139)
- London Child Guidance Clinic and Training Center - Moodie, William - Correspondence, 1929-1936 (Box 13, Folder 140)
- London Child Guidance Clinic and Training Center - Moodie, William - Correspondence, 1929-1936 (Box 13, Folder 141)
- London Child Guidance Clinic and Training Center - Norman, Priscilla W. - Correspondence, 1931-1934 (Box 13, Folder 142)
- London Child Guidance Clinic and Training Center - Norman, Priscilla W. - Correspondence, 1935-1937 (Box 14, Folder 143)
- London Child Guidance Clinic and Training Center - Norman, Priscilla W. - Correspondence, 1935-1937 (Box 14, Folder 144)
- London Child Guidance Clinic and Training Center - Procedure Regulations and Constitutions, 1931-1937 (Box 14, Folder 145)
- London Child Guidance Clinic and Training Center - Statistical Monthly Reports and Memoranda, 1929-1940 (Box 14, Folder 146)
- London Child Guidance Clinic and Training Center - Statistical Monthly Reports and Memoranda, 1929-1940 (Box 14, Folder 147)
- London Child Guidance Clinic and Training Center - Statistical Monthly Reports and Memoranda, 1929-1940 (Box 14, Folder 148)